<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<gantrytips>

	<tip label="How To Install The Slider?">
		<![CDATA[
		The responsive slider is only available for the pro version of this template.
                <br/><br/>
                After purchasing and downloading this template, the slider installs with the template.
                <br/><br/>
                Once the template and module have been successfully installed, head to the Joomla! Module Manager and find "Responsive Slide Show".
                <br/><br/>
                Add the images for the slider in "Setup" => "File Paths" by separating each image file by a comma. The paths must be relative or starting with http://<br/><br/>
                Assign the module to the showcase-a position, choose for what menu items the slider should appear and publish.
                If you want to add HTML to appear over your images, just use the HTML editor and separate each page by a page-break (see pagebreak at the bottom). Must be following the index of available image!
                ]]>
	</tip>
        <tip label="How To Change Colors?">
            <![CDATA[
            Color options for this template are only available in the pro version.
            <br/><br/>
            Changing colors is simple: Go to the Colors tab of this template and choose the right colors as desired.
            <br/><br/>
            Keep in mind that we heavily use filters and lighten up some color codes in the module positions to keep smooth gradients, no matter what color has been selected.
            If you want dark color tones, then please user a much more darkened version of the color you want to use.
            <br/><br/>
            Best is you'll play around with the color options for each area of your website one-by-one, starting with links and then all the way down for the module positions you are using.
            ]]>
        </tip>
        <tip label="What else is there for me?">
            <![CDATA[
            See the Features tab of this template. There you can enable or disable a variety of features that ship with this template such as fixed menus, rounded or normal menus, To-Top button and many more!
            ]]>
        </tip>
-->
</gantrytips>